https://theadsgroup.com/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy
General Information
Use of this website signifies your acknowledgement and consent to this privacy policy. The ADS Group takes your privacy seriously and is committed to safeguarding your confidentiality online. We collect and record your data as a result of your sharing this information with us. This may, for instance be information you have entered into our contact form.
In addition, our computer servers record user system data when you visit our website. This data consists primarily of technical information, such as web browser, operating system or the time the site was accessed. This information is collected and stored automatically when you visit our website.
We have established this privacy policy to assist you in understanding the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of your personal information. This privacy policy discloses the types of personal information we gather, how it is used, and how you can gain access to and edit any data that we have collected about you at any time.
Guiding principles
Our privacy policy has been developed using the following guiding principles:
The ADS Group collects personal information online primarily to provide our visitors with a more relevant experience on this website. When doing so, we will make every reasonable effort to avoid excessive or irrelevant collection of data. We will take reasonable measures to safeguard and secure your personal information through the employment of protected databases on secured servers with restricted and limited access.
Disclosure of personal information
The ADS Group does not sell or trade user’s personal information to third parties. We will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent, as required or permitted by law, and to provide the features and services you have requested.
Security
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and adhere to industry best practices to ensure it is not lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. This website is hosted on servers located in the United States. As such, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States. Any personal information you provide during your visit will be processed and maintained on our web server and other internal systems located within the United States.
Non-personally identifiable data
Anytime you visit this website, we may gather certain non-personally identifiable information regarding the means you used to access our site. This information may include the type and version of your browser, your service provider, your IP address and any search engine you may have used to locate this site. We use this information to assist in the diagnoses of problems with our server, administration of the website and to compile broad statistical data. In addition, we gather certain navigational information about where you go on this website. This information enables us to determine which areas of the website are most frequently visited and helps us to adapt the site to the need and interests of our online visitors. Information of this type is gathered in the aggregate and will not be associated with a specific individual without that individual’s consent.
Use of cookies
The ADS Group may use a browser feature known as a “cookie”. Cookies are small text files placed on your computer that assist us in providing you with an efficient browsing experience. We use cookies to provide you with the convenience of not having to re-enter information, such as IDs and passwords, multiple times during your visits to this website.
Most of the cookies we employ are referred to session cookies which are deleted after you leave our website. Other cookies will remain archived on your device until you delete them. These cookies enable us to recognize your browser the next time you visit our website.
Cookies may also be utilized to help us provide you with information targeted to your interests, based upon your prior browsing history on this website. You may elect to not permit the use of cookies; the help section under the toolbar on most browsers will instruct you on how to disable this feature. Please note, this website was designed to take advantage of the use of cookies, should you elect to configure your browser to decline their use, certain features of this web site may not function correctly.
Personal information voluntarily provided
Any information you provide to us when requesting information, or use any other interactive portions of this website may be used to provide you with information you have requested about our company, and our services. You may opt out of receiving future communications at any time; see opt-out procedures below. This data may also be used to enhance your experience on this website by providing content that is most relevant to your interests.
Opt-out procedure
You have the right at any time to withdraw your consent for us to contact you, or disclose your personal
information, once it has been provided, by contacting us at website@theadsgroup.com or mailing us at:
The ADS Group
2155 Niagara Lane North Plymouth, Minnesota USA 55447 Attn: Website
2155 Niagara Lane NorthPlymouth, MN 55447-4654Get DirectionsPhone: 800.759.0992Fax: 763.449.5555sales@theadsgroup.com
Latest News
HoloDisc
Hot off the press. The ADS Group presents Holodisc. It’ Read More
Latest Work
ADS Video Brochure
